Hello, I am Chanel Patel and I am going to
show you L&T
Finance and L&T Finance, see,
in recent times, it had made a high of
108 ₹1 note
and just now, after that, a slight
correction is seen in this stock, it
came around that time and now
you can see this stock anytime in it
and here, right now,
this stock is at 94090 paise and you still have a chance
and if I look at it, I have put a weekly
chart here, I have put a one-day chart,
this chart is one day and
here, if I put a weekly chart, then
you will see here that this week
also, how tremendous growth has been seen in this stock
in the chart, you can see
that such a huge growth has been seen, it has
almost doubled the money,
now look here, if you open
this account from Rs. 56, then
your money has almost doubled,
I have put a weekly chart, please pay attention to this
and here I have put a monthly chart,
so you will see this  This high is
so high, if you show it to me, it is
approximately 198, it is from 2017,
and this is a company of such a group
that it will give you a tremendous performance,
this company of the Plassey & Toubro group is a
very big group, and
look here, when this stock came due to this, look at it,
almost look at it, while falling,
it had made a low of 42 rupees,
a balance low of that, then after that,
this stock saw a strong rise and as soon as the
rise is seen, you can see,
I told you here that it had made a high of approximately 111 rupees, okay, so
look at it from there,
if we look at its high, see, it
made a high of 113 here,
after making a high of 113, because from here the money has
almost doubled, so a little
correction will definitely be seen, see a little
correction was seen, and this free
stock is trending here right now, just like the
trend was going on here, similarly the
trend has continued on opportunities, you still have a chance,
this is a reminder to pick up the stock
and  If you take a look here and
fold it for 1 to 2 years, you will
also see that almost this
high of friends will also be broken
and you will get to see a multibagger return
in this company
and see, the second thing is that
if I shorten this square a little, you will see here
if I shorten the candy then you should have
seen
that first
its IPO came in 2012 and
when it got listed, see here
ghee so much that a
little dip from here or
after that this stock saw a huge rise
and only a little correction was seen in
this system and then such a rally took place
that it almost quadrupled the money
and then due to a comment there was a decline in that stock,
then it came to the same level,
see, you see the label is just empty, then it
came to the same level
and here the same father had risen,
then there was a decline, this is where the boss save is
adopting, then there was a rise, then there was a decline,
then a bag from here  A very tremendous
rally was formed and Save is trying to form a similar rally
here
that you will not do all these things here,
if this is your old one, then it has
once again repeated the
9th old things and this time you will again get at
least two to two and a half times till Dwara Dham,
your money here will become two to two and a half times
and what you have to do, you see here,
what you have to do now is you have not bought a bag of goods here,
I have not bought a bag of goods, slowly slowly slowly
you keep picking up the goods,
how slowly slowly slowly you picked up the goods,
now you have picked up the temple, in the same way
you will keep picking up the goods, now
you should invest here for a long-term purpose,
wait for a few days, it will
give you tremendous returns
because any multi group is a
tremendous group, that is, it is a very big
group, the company of this group never
steps back, it will give you multifold returns one day or the other,
so you should keep these things in mind
and a very tremendous one here  It is a challenge
and let me take you to its website
and I will try to show you here, if
you look here if I
go to the fundamentals then look at the piece of its stock here
and on the sector it is almost
moving around and look here
it is not giving a return of about 70 per cent in one year,
see it has given a return of 70 per cent in one year,
in one month it has given a
return of about minus point 50 per cent here,
but it has a return of 70 per cent in air,
very strong in debt and humanities,
Lofty dynasty and also assume that from 13 to 40,
this company is a midcap, you can see here it is a
midcap, it is a driver, C fans and we
see that according to this, the
performance of this stock, it is also
very important to see things, write profit and loss,
we have come to profit and loss, it is
very important to see things and here
we will talk about net profit, if
we talk about real profit then
here you see
that  Net profit of 260 crores in March-2010 Net profit of
3091 crores in March-2011
Net profit of 455 crores in 2012
730 crores in March-2013 597 crores in 2014
Here the written has gone down a bit
and here there has been a huge jump,
see now
in 2015 there was a
net profit of 8055 crores, in 2016 there is a
net profit of 857 crores, in 2017 there
is a net profit of 1042 crores, in 2018 there
is a net profit of 125 crores and see in
2019 such a tremendous boom was seen in the stock
that almost
MP3's
net profit of 2226 crores, a
huge jump in profit was seen
and here in March 2019,
due to Kuwait in March 2019,
see, there has been a decline in this stock, still
from almost other quarters
Stock means this quarter is bullish,
except for the A quarter, net profit of about 17 crores
and here, if
you look at the quarter of March 2021, there is a profit of 90 crores,
still it is okay, so even now
in this quarter and in the coming quarters,
you will see more bullishness here
because when this stock
is performing like this, then
in the coming quarters you will get
to see even better response here, so you
still have a chance, you
can make a good money by investing in a good stock here, okay, thank you, thank you.